salsabil tarek

FrontEnd Developer

salsabil.tarek55@gmail.com

581734214

Riyad, Saudi Arabia



After Year of Experience i can combine the art of design with the art of programming. Responsibilities will include translation of the UI/UX design

wireframes to actual code that will produce visual elements of the application. I will work with the UI/UX designer and bridge the

WORK EXPERIENCE

graphical design and technical implementation, Wordpress Devloper

OneHoster

Full-time

2017 - 2018

Front-End Developer

Pharous

Full-time

08/2018 - 09/2019

Front-End Developer

2019 - Present

Full-time

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Help Blind People

2011 - Present

Resala Charity

Follow my profile on:

O Linked in:

linkedin.com/in/salsabil-tarek-630088a6/

O Github:

https://salsabil55.github.io/profile/

SKILLS

WORDPRESS

HTML

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

JQUERY

ANGULAR

PUGJS

MEDIA QUERY

SASS

Git

GulpJs

PROJECTS

Eldawi sons

Tycoon-Egypt

MSG Egypt

Marj3

Grow

Odem

Pharama Catle

Belshifa

Egyption Medical Syndivate

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Faculty Of Science Bachelor from Alexandria

Very Good 2011 - 2015 University

CONFERENCES & COURSES

WebDeveloper Diploma (2016)

New Horizon

Angular Basic Development (2019) udemy

INTERESTS

Motion Design

Animations